A Guide to the Papers of Henry Heth, 1765-1800
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Accounts and receipts for 1804 1804 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from David Patterson 1805 Jan 3 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from John Davidson 1805 Jan 13 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Charles A. Bradford 1805 Jan 26 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Peter Nelson 1805 Feb 3 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from A. Nicolson 1805 Feb 9 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Richard Brooke 1805 Feb 17 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from John Davidson 1805 Mar 5 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from William Randolph 1805 [Mar 6] (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from J. P. Pleasants 1805 Mar 8 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Hervey Heth 1805 Mar 9 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from John Wicklam 1805 Apr 10 (Box 3)
- Letter from William Porsegum to Harry Heth 1805 Apr 10 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from William Heth 1805 Apr 10 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from A. Nicolson 1805 Apr 17 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from W. P. Pleasants 1805 Apr 19 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from William Forsce 1805 May 4 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from William Forsce 1805 Jun 4 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Richard Brooke 1805 Jun 7 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from John Gill 1805 Jun 27 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from John Stewart 1805 Jul 2 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from H. G. Heth 1805 Jul 7 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Snydam & Wychoff 1805 Jul 12 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from John Davidson 1805 Aug 8 (Box 3)
- Statement from W. LaPrade 1805 Aug 20 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from William Heth 1805 Aug 23 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from William Randolph [1805 Sep] (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from John Gill 1805 Sep 7 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from William Bentley 1805 Sep 10 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from James Scott 1805 Sep 16 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from A. Nicolson 1805 Sep 19 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Benjamin Dabney 1805 Sep 22 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from William Fitzhugh 1805 Nov 12 (Box 3)
- Extract from deed-Sowell to Ronald 1805 Dec 10 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from George Hay 1805 Dec 15 (Box 3)
- Extract of deed-Brummal to Salle 1805 Dec 23 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Phillip Coghill 1805 Dec 28 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from David Patterson 1805 Dec 29 (Box 3)
- Accounts and receipts for 1805 1805 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from William Forsce 1806 Jan 1 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from James Scott 1806 Jan 18 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from William Banks 1806 Jan 27 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Charles A. H. Bradford 1806 Feb 12 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Peter Field Fannan 1806 May 17 (Box 3)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Peter Field Fannan 1806 Jul 5 (Box 3)
- Harry Heth vs. John Swann & George Taylor 1806 Sep 16 (Box 3)
- Agreement between David Ross and James Corrie 1806 May 26 (Box 3)
- Accounts and receipts for 1806 1806 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from William Smith 1807 Jan 3 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Mr. Railey 1807 Jan 7 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Peter Duprey 1807 Jan 7 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from William J. Banks 1807 Jan 13 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from J. Waise 1807 Jan 15 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from John Davidson 1807 Jan 16 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Joseph Tidball 1807 Jan 21 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from A. Cowley 1807 Jan 27 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from John Tayloe 1807 Jan 27 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from John Harvis 1807 Jan 29 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from William Pope 1807 Feb 7 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from James Scott 1807 Feb 9 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from A. Nicolson 1807 Feb 10 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from John Gile 1807 Feb 11 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Edward Wooldridge 1807 Feb 12 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Eliza Heth 1807 Feb 12 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Thomas Tredway 1807 Feb 12 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from A. Nicolson 1807 Feb 14 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from A. Nicolson 1807 Feb 16 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Thomas Tredway 1807 Feb 19 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from John Swann 1807 Feb 20 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from J. P. Pleasants 1807 Feb 22 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from J. P. Pleasants 1807 Feb 23 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from A. Nicolson 1807 Feb 24 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from J. P. Pleasants 1807 Feb 25 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Henry Cary 1807 Feb 25 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Nat Perkins 1807 Mar 1 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from D. M. Randolph 1807 Mar 2 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Samuel S. Goodson 1807 Mar 2 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Robert Perkins 1807 Mar 3 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from George M. Crecke & A. Nicolson 1807 Mar 6 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Henry Thompson 1807 Mar 7 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Abram S. Wooldridge 1807 Mar 8 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from J. P. Pleasants 1807 Mar 8 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from J. P. Pleasants 1807 Mar 12 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from A. Nicolson 1807 Mar 15 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Charles A. H. Bradford 1807 Apr 14 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from A. Nicolson 1807 Apr 16 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from J. P. Pleasants 1807 Apr 19 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from John Harris 1807 Apr 21 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from J. P. Pleasants 1807 Apr 23 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from A. Nicolson 1807 Apr 25 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Archibald Wooldridge 1807 Apr 27 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from George McCredie 1807 May 3 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Archibald McRae 1807 May 6 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from James Scott 1807 May 6 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from James Scott 1807 May 7 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from A. Nicolson 1807 May 7 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Thomas Taylor 1807 May 8 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Thomas Hay 1807 May 8 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from James Rowland 1807 May 9 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from J. Heth 1807 May 10 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from A. Nicolson 1807 May 10 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from H. G. Heth 1807 May 13 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from A. Nicolson 1807 May 22 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from C. Randolph 1807 May 22 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from A. Lannohile 1807 May 26 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Theodore Armistead 1807 Jun 5 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Cary Selden 1807 Jun 7 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Adam Craig 1807 Jun 10 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from H. G. Heth 1807 Jun 11 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from James Martin 1807 Jun 17 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Richard B. Goode 1807 Jun 18 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Henry G. Heth 1807 Jun 23 (Box 4)
- Bond-Thompson Blunt & Harry Heth to Thomas Wooldridge 1807 Jun 24 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from H. G. Heth 1807 Jun 24 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from J. Pleasants 1807 Jun 29 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from H. G. Heth 1807 Jul 3 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from George Smith 1807 Jul 8 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth or John Cundiff from Edward Moseley 1807 Jul 8 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Samuel Dyer 1807 Jul 9 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from J. P. Pleasants 1807 Jul 10 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from A. C. Randolph 1807 Jul 11 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from R. Gample 1807 Jul 11 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from A. C. Randolph 1807 Jul 22 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Joseph Tidball 1807 Jul 28 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from James Caruthers 1807 Aug 1 (Box 4)
- Letter to Andrew Nicolson from Robert Perkins 1807 Aug 4 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Benjamin Hawkins 1807 Aug 5 (Box 4)
- Letter to [?] from H. Heth 1807 Aug 11 (Box 4)
- Letter to Harry Heth from Peter Field Farrar 1807 Aug 12 (Box 4)
- Letter from William Marshall to Harry Heth 1807 Aug 19 (Box 4)
- Letter from Theo. Armistead to Harry Heth 1807 Aug 20 (Box 4)
- Letter from J. C. Mongrand to Harry Heth 1807 Aug 25 (Box 4)
- Letter from A. Nicholson to Harry Heth 1807 Aug (Box 4)
- Letter from Robert Hert to M. M. Glen 1807 Sep 9 (Box 4)
- Letter from John Davidson to Harry Heth 1807 Sep 19 (Box 4)
- Letter from James Martin to Harry Heth 1807 Oct 12 (Box 4)
- Deed, Thomas Wooldridge to Harry Heth 1807 Oct 29 (Box 4)
- Deed, Arch Wooldridge and Edith Harris Wooldridge to Harry Heth 1807 Oct 29 (Box 4)
- Letter from D. Randolph to Harry Heth 1807 Nov 1 (Box 4)
- Letter from Peter Manifoto to Harry Heth 1807 Nov 3 (Box 4)
- Letter from Theo. Armistead to Harry Heth 1807 Nov 5 (Box 4)
- Letter from A. Nicholson to Harry Heth 1807 Nov 16 (Box 4)
- Letter from A. Nicholson to Harry Heth 1807 Nov 18 (Box 4)
- Letter from Morgan Neville to Harry Heth 1807 Dec 15 (Box 4)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1807 Dec 17 (Box 4)
- Letter from Isham Britton to Henry Heth 1807 Dec 20 (Box 4)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1807 Dec 21 (Box 4)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1807 Dec 28 (Box 4)
- Accounts and receipts for 1807 1807 (Box 4)
- Summons of Martin Railey 1808 Feb 15 (Box 4)
- Letter from Harvey Heth to Harry Heth 1808 Mar 27 (Box 4)
- Letter from James Henderson to Mssrs. Nicolson and Heth 1808 Mar 28 (Box 4)
- Letter from John Hill to Harry Heth 1808 Mar 29 (Box 4)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1808 Apr 2 (Box 4)
- Lawsuit, Martin vs Sclater 1808 Apr 12 (Box 4)
- Letter from Lund Hopkins to Harry Heth 1808 Jun 2 (Box 4)
- Letter from A. C. Randolph to Harry Heth 1808 Jun 13 (Box 4)
- Letter from Lament Clark to Harry Heth 1808 Jun 13 (Box 4)
- Letter from James Scott to Harry Heth 1808 Jun 29 (Box 4)
- Letter, [D. M. Randolph to Harry Heth] 1808 Jul 19 (Box 4)
- Deed of trust, Farrar to Harry Heth 1808 Jul 22 (Box 4)
- Letter from A. C. Randolph to Harry Heth 1808 Jul 26 (Box 4)
- Letter from B. Randolph to Harry Heth 1808 Jul 30 (Box 4)
- Letter from James Pleasants to Peter Duprey 1808 Jul 31 (Box 4)
- Letter from Arch McRae to Harry Heth 1808 Aug 1 (Box 4)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1808 Aug 15 (Box 4)
- Letter from D. M. Randolph to Harry Heth 1808 Aug 22 (Box 4)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1808 Aug 22 (Box 4)
- Letter from Joseph Tidball to Harry Heth 1808 Aug 29 (Box 4)
- Letter from Peter Duprey to Harry Heth 1808 Sep 6 (Box 4)
- Sale of Negroes to A. B. Randolph 1808 Sep 10 (Box 4)
- Letter from H. Holmes 1808 Sep 16 (Box 4)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1808 Sep 17 (Box 4)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1808 Sep 21 (Box 4)
- Letter John Hollornfelt to Harry Heth 1808 Sep 28 (Box 4)
- Letter from H. Heth to G. L. R. Daily 1808 Oct 16 (Box 4)
- Letter from Richard Brooke to Harry Heth 1808 Oct 16 (Box 4)
- Letter from T. H. Drew to the surveyer of Chesterfield 1808 Oct 26 (Box 4)
- Letter from D. Meade to Harry Heth 1808 Oct 27 (Box 4)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1808 Nov 12 (Box 4)
- Bond, William and Peter Minor Cary to Harry Heth 1808 Nov 15 (Box 4)
- Letter from L. Washington to Gen. Jas. Wood 1808 Nov 29 (Box 4)
- Unidentified [1808?] (Box 4)
- Accounts and receipts for 1808 1808 (Box 5)
- Articles of co-partnery between Andrew Nicolson, Harry Heth, Peter B. Randolph, and Edward D. Digges 1809 Jan 1 (Box 5)
- Letter from E. D. Digges to Harry Heth 1809 Mar 22 (Box 5)
- Letter from John Heth to Harry Heth 1809 Mar 25 (Box 5)
- Letter from Oliver Evans to Messrs. Nicolson and Heth 1809 Apr 5 (Box 5)
- Letter from William Kimbrough to Harry Heth 1809 Apr 13 (Box 5)
- Articles of Agreement between Harry Heth and George Hanto 1809 Apr 14 (Box 5)
- Deed, E. O. Branch to Harry Heth 1809 May 2 (Box 5)
- Letter from Peter F. Smith to Harry Heth 1809 Jul 16 (Box 5)
- Receipt from L. H. Givandin 1809 Aug 21 (Box 5)
- Note from Sarah Brown to Nicolson and Heth 1809 Sep 26 (Box 5)
- Deed, John Harvie to Harry Heth 1809 Oct 10 (Box 5)
- Letter from Henry Banks to Harry Heth 1809 Oct 21 (Box 5)
- Opinion of George Hay on leases 1809 Oct 31 (Box 5)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Roland Randolph 1809 Nov 12 (Box 5)
- Deed, Samuel and Catherine Clark to Harry Heth and James Brown 1809 Dec 8 (Box 5)
- Jas. Temple to Harry Heth 1809 Dec 22 (Box 5)
- Letter from A. Tannehill to Harry Heth 1809 Dec 25 (Box 5)
- Letter from Turner Christian to Harry Heth 1809 Dec 27 (Box 5)
- Accounts and receipts for 1809 1809 (Box 5)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Henry Heth [180?] (Box 5)
- Letter from Richard Brooke to Harry Heth 1810 Jan 6 (Box 5)
- Letter from Turner Christian to Harry Heth 1810 Jan 11 (Box 5)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1810 Jan 13 (Box 5)
- Letter from Allan McRae to Harry Heth 1810 Jan 15 (Box 5)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1810 Jan 17 (Box 5)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1810 Jan 19 (Box 5)
- Letter from W. Ward to William Randolph 1810 Jan 25 (Box 5)
- Letter from James Scott to Harry Heth 1810 Jan 29 (Box 5)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1810 Jan 29 (Box 5)
- Letter from Daniel Trabue to Harry Heth 1810 Jan 29 (Box 5)
- Letter from J. Monteiro to Messrs. Munteiros and company 1810 Jan 30 (Box 5)
- Letter from William Marshall to Harry Heth 1810 Feb 2 (Box 5)
- Letter from A. Blair to Harry Heth 1810 Feb 3 (Box 5)
- Letter from William Marshall to Harry Heth 1810 Feb 3 (Box 5)
- Letter from John Fowler to Harry Heth 1810 Feb 6 (Box 5)
- Letter from J. P. Hunnicut to Henry Heth 1810 Feb 10 (Box 5)
- Letter from Sam H. Saunders to Harry Heth 1810 Feb 26 (Box 5)
- Letter from Henry Lee to Harry Heth 1810 Feb 27 (Box 5)
- Letter from Richard Randolph to Harry Heth 1810 Mar 13 (Box 5)
- Letter from Richard Randolph to Harry Heth 1810 Mar 14 (Box 5)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1810 Mar 22 (Box 5)
- Letter from H. J. Bumley to Mr. and Mrs. Harry Heth 1810 Mar 23 (Box 5)
- Letter from John B. Armistead to Harry Heth 1810 Mar 26 (Box 5)
- Letter from J. Munteiro to Harry Heth 1810 Mar 26 (Box 5)
- Letter from Sarah Barker to Harry Heth 1810 Mar 20 (Box 5)
- Letter from Sam H. Saunders to Harry Heth 1810 Mar 29 (Box 5)
- Memo from A. Nicolson to Harry Heth 1810 Mar 30 (Box 5)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1810 Apr 7 (Box 5)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1810 Apr 11 (Box 5)
- Letter from Thomas Miller to Harry Heth 1810 Apr 18 (Box 5)
- Letter from George Easterly to Harry Heth 1810 Apr 18 (Box 5)
- Bond-Peter E. Bentley & Joseph Bentley to Harry Heth 1810 Apr 25 (Box 5)
- Letter from John Granberry to Harry Heth 1810 May 1 (Box 5)
- Letter from Henry Heth to Harry Heth 1810 May 3 (Box 5)
- Letter from A. Nicholson to Harry Heth 1810 May 12 (Box 5)
- Letter from Paul J. Donaldson to Augustus Davis 1810 May 31 (Box 5)
- Letter from George Easterly to Harry Heth 1810 Jun 3 (Box 5)
- Letter from J. Monteiro to Harry Heth 1810 Jan 30 (Box 5)
- Letter from George Harris to Harry Heth 1810 Jun 8 (Box 5)
- Note - Zephania McGender to Nicolson & Heth 1810 Jun 12 (Box 5)
- Contract between Zephania McGender & Nicolson, Heth & Co. 1810 Jun 12 (Box 5)
- Letter from H. G. Heth to Harry Heth 1810 Jun 15 (Box 5)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to Harry Heth 1810 Jun 18 (Box 5)
- Bill of sale-Erasmus Reamus to Harry Heth 1810 Jun 21 (Box 5)
- Letter from John Severn to Harry Heth 1810 Jun 28 (Box 5)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1810 Jun 28 (Box 5)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1810 Jul 2 (Box 5)
- Letter from Edward O. Branch to Harry Heth 1810 Jul 8 (Box 5)
- Letter from David Homnoy to Harry Heth 1810 Jul 12 (Box 5)
- Letter from Edward Bennett to Harry Heth 1810 Jul 13 (Box 5)
- Letter from David Street to Harry Heth 1810 Jul 21 (Box 5)
- Letter from V. Gray to Harry Heth 1810 Jul 25 (Box 5)
- Letter from John Stewart to Harry Heth 1810 Jul 27 (Box 5)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1810 Aug 1 (Box 5)
- Letter from B. Randolph to Harry Heth 1810 Aug 24 (Box 5)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1810 Aug 8 (Box 5)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1810 Aug 17 (Box 5)
- Letter from B. Randolph to Harry Heth 1810 Aug 24 (Box 5)
- Letter from B. Randolph to Harry Heth 1810 Aug 25 (Box 5)
- Letter from David Street to Harry Heth 1810 Aug 25 (Box 5)
- Letter from Augustine Davis to Harry Heth 1810 Sep 5 (Box 5)
- Letter from Samuel Woody to Harry Heth 1810 Oct (Box 5)
- Letter from B. Randolph to Harry Heth 1810 Nov 13 (Box 5)
- Letter from John Dawson to Harry Heth 1810 Nov 29 (Box 5)
- Agreement between Daniel Trabue & Harry Heth 1810 Dec 1 (Box 5)
- Articles of Copartnery between Harry Heth, Beverley Randolph, & Edward D. Digges 1810 Dec 10 (Box 5)
- Letter from Gabriel Peterson to Harry Heth 1810 Dec 12 (Box 5)
- Power of attorney - Martin Railey to John Railey 1810 Dec 9 (Box 5)
- Agreement between J. Railey, Harry Heth, & Martin Railey 1810 Dec 13 (Box 5)
- Inventory of goods, chattels of John Heth 1810 Nov 18 (Box 5)
- Appraisal of property of John Heth's estate 1810 Dec 17 (Box 5)
- Letter from Robert L. Hackley to William Randolph 1810 Dec 18 (Box 5)
- Deed-James & Ann Howard to Samuel Taylor & James Scott 1810 Dec 20 (Box 5)
- Note-Martha Randolph & Harry Heth to William Royall 1810 Dec 31 (Box 5)
- Accounts and receipts for 1810 1810 (Box 5)
- Opinion of George Hay on John Barker's will 1811 Jan 4 (Box 5)
- Letter from William Bentley to Harry Heth 1811 Jan 6 (Box 5)
- Letter from J. McLung to Harry Heth 1811 Jan 21 (Box 5)
- Bond-Harry Heth & Peter B. Randolph to Charles Caplan & John John H. Brown 1811 Jan 1 (Box 5)
- Deed-Woodford Alvis to Edward Burnette 1811 Jan 30 (Box 5)
- Agreement between Daniel Trabue and Harry Heth 1811 Feb 4 (Box 5)
- Letter from John E. Meade to Harry Heth 1811 Jan 2 (Box 5)
- Letter from William Bentley to Harry Heth 1811 Feb 15 (Box 5)
- Note-Harry Heth & John Cundiffe to Edward Wooldridge 1811 Feb 16 (Box 5)
- Bond-Harry Heth & P. B. Randolph to the estate of Andrew Nicolson 1811 Mar 18 (Box 5)
- Bond-Peter B. Randolph & Harry Heth to Judith Nicolson 1811 Mar 18 (Box 5)
- Letter from Joseph Brown to William Randolph 1811 Feb 31 (Box 5)
- Letter from Samuel Watkins to Harry Heth 1811 Apr 2 (Box 5)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1811 Apr 5 (Box 5)
- Letter from William Bentley to Harry Heth 1811 Apr 7 (Box 5)
- Letter from Edmund Randolph to Harry Heth 1811 Apr 23 (Box 5)
- Letter from Vincent Gray to Harry Heth 1811 May 4 (Box 5)
- Letter from C. & R. Railey to Harry Heth 1811 May 9 (Box 5)
- Letter from John Stewart to Harry Heth 1811 Jun 8 (Box 5)
- Letter from H. G. Heth to Harry Heth 1811 Jun 12 (Box 5)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1811 Jun 12 (Box 5)
- Letter from Alexander Stewart to Harry Heth 1811 Jun 15 (Box 5)
- Letter from William Gilkeson to Harry Heth 1811 Jun 18 (Box 5)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1811 Jun 22 (Box 5)
- Letter from Alexander Stewart to Harry Heth 1811 Jun 27 (Box 5)
- Letter from Samuel Smith to Harry Heth 1811 Jul 6 (Box 5)
- Letter from Henry Heth to Harry Heth 1811 Jul 6 (Box 5)
- Letter from Samuel Smith to Harry Heth 1811 Jul 10 (Box 6)
- Letter from Thomas Irvin to Harry Heth 1811 Jul 8 (Box 6)
- Letter from Theo. Armistead to Harry Heth 1811 Jul 8 (Box 6)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1811 Jul 8 (Box 6)
- Letter from Miles Cary to Harry Heth 1811 Jul 9 (Box 6)
- Letter from Sally Wooldridge to Harry Heth 1811 Jul 10 (Box 6)
- Letter from Seth Speman to Harry Heth 1811 Jul 10 (Box 6)
- Letter from Samuel Taylor to Harry Heth 1811 Jul 10 (Box 6)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1811 Jul 11 (Box 6)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1811 Jul 12 (Box 6)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Leth and Spenser 1811 Jul 15 (Box 6)
- Letter from Henry Heth to Harry Heth 1811 Jul 9 (Box 6)
- Unidentified letter 1811 Jul 20 (Box 6)
- Letter from Peter H. Thomas to Harry Heth 1811 Jul 25 (Box 6)
- Letter from William Heth to Harry Heth 1811 Jul 27 (Box 6)
- Letter from Henry Banks to Harry Heth 1811 Jul 25 (Box 6)
- Letter from D. Meade to Harry Heth 1811 Jul 29 (Box 6)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1811 Jul 29 (Box 6)
- Letter from Willis Swann to Harry Heth 1811 Aug (Box 6)
- Letter from William Archer to Harry Heth 1811 Aug (Box 6)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1811 Aug 5 (Box 6)
- Letter from Theodore Armistead to Harry Heth 1811 Aug 8 (Box 6)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1811 Aug 8 (Box 6)
- Letter from Alexander Stewart to Harry Heth 1811 Aug 10 (Box 6)
- Letter from Theodore Stevenson to Harry Heth 1811 Aug 12 (Box 6)
- Letter from William Archer to Harry Heth 1811 Aug 16 (Box 6)
- Letter from Harry Heth to B. C. Stannan 1811 Aug 17 (Box 6)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1811 Aug 20 (Box 6)
- Letter from David Patterson to Harry Heth 1811 Aug 21 (Box 6)
- Letter from David Meade to Harry Heth 1811 Aug 22 (Box 6)
- Letter from Lawrence Muse to Harry Heth 1811 Aug 22 (Box 6)
- Memo of lease, Elizabeth Allen to Harry Heth 1811 Aug 24 (Box 6)
- Letter from Alexander Stewart to Harry Heth 1811 Aug 28 (Box 6)
- Letter from Harry Heth to John Cundiffe 1811 Aug 28 (Box 6)
- Letter from Edward Moseley to Harry Heth 1811 Aug 29 (Box 6)
- Letter from Harry Heth to John Cundiffe 1811 Aug 29 (Box 6)
- Letter from John Cundiffe to W. H. Heth 1811 Aug 29 (Box 6)
- Letter from Jonathan Carleton and Ephraim Robins to Harry Heth 1811 Aug 29 (Box 6)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1811 Sep 3 (Box 6)
- Letter from Peter Porter to Harry Heth 1811 Sep 4 (Box 6)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1811 Sep 4 (Box 6)
- Letter from Thomas Railey to Harry Heth 1811 Sep 11 (Box 6)
- Letter from H. G. Heth to Harry Heth 1811 Sep 12 (Box 6)
- Letter from Edward Johnson to Harry Heth 1811 Sep 14 (Box 6)
- Letter from Edward D. Digges to Harry Heth 1811 Sep 15 (Box 6)
- Letter from William Mayo to Harry Heth 1811 Sep 20 (Box 6)
- Letter from J. Mc Clung to Dr. Johnson 1811 Sep 20 (Box 6)
- Letter from Lawrence Muse to Harry Heth 1811 Sep 22 (Box 6)
- Letter from Ephream Robins to Harry Heth 1811 Sep 23 (Box 6)
- Letter from John Davidson to Harry Heth 1811 Sep 26 (Box 6)
- Letter from Edward Taylor to Harry Heth 1811 Sep 27 (Box 6)
- Letter from Samuel Dyer to Harry Heth 1811 Sep 30 (Box 6)
- Letter from C. L. Coplan to Harry Heth 1811 Oct 4 (Box 6)
- Letter from D. Meade to Harry Heth 1811 Oct 8 (Box 6)
- Letter from Alexander Stewart to Harry Heth 1811 Oct 16 (Box 6)
- Letter from Stetwaggon and Knight to Harry Heth 1811 Oct 16 (Box 6)
- Letter from D. M. Randolph to Harry Heth 1811 Oct 17 (Box 6)
- Memo of dissolution: Harry Heth, Bevr. Randolph, and Edward D. Digges 1811 Oct 19 (Box 6)
- Dissolution of the firm of Heth, Randolph & Digges 1811 Oct 19 (Box 6)
- Letter from Samuel L. Smith to Harry Heth 1811 Oct 20 (Box 6)
- Letter from Harry Heth 1811 Oct 22 (Box 6)
- Deed, James Kilten to Samuel Taylor and Lawson Burfoote 1811 Oct 24 (Box 6)
- Memo, Harry Heth to J. Salle 1811 Oct 28 (Box 6)
- Debts due to Nicolson and Heth 1811 Oct (Box 6)
- Letter from Vincent Gray to Harry Heth 1811 Nov 3 (Box 6)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1811 Nov 11 (Box 6)
- Letter from Hervey Heth to Harry Heth 1811 Nov 17 (Box 6)
- Letter from David Patterson to Harry Heth 1811 Nov 21 (Box 6)
- Letter from Vincent Gray to Harry Heth 1811 Nov 23 (Box 6)
- Letter from Harry Heth to William Hay 1811 Nov 23 (Box 6)
- Letter from Benjamin Botts to Harry Heth 1811 Nov 25 (Box 6)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1811 Nov 25 (Box 6)
- Letter from Lindy Hopkins to Harry Heth 1811 Nov 29 (Box 6)
- Letter from Thomas Irvin to Harry Heth 1811 Nov 29 (Box 6)
- Memo between Peter Porter and Harry Heth 1811 Nov 29 (Box 6)